We have the communication, the bias, the system's priority, the system's priority.
Father God has become the core of this meeting.
We just ask that you may bless us as we go through our business and the city's business.
We lift up the city in Miami.
It's residents and flears.
It's employees.
We just ask that you may guide them with blessing.
Father God, give us this protection as we go home and as we depart.
We love you so much.
Amen.
Father God leads us to the flag of the United States of America.
And to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation, another God.
Indivisible with liberty and justice for all.
Public input.
Let's go to the personal appearances.
Five.
Pointless.
Much to proof.
Second.
Hi.
Don't go.
James.
Science claims less demands for a branch forward.
Maybe a proof Second?
Please.
I suppose.
Hi.
James.
Garас.
Spebs 10.
Seven minutes on the January 21st, 25 regular meeting.
Motion the proof.
Different should.
imes.
He steps.
Hi.
Thank you.
Athena they busy in Forcubvisor's question.
to this agenda.
Just to be community announcements, Tim, this may well be continued from the council chambers
and reached main to the staff rooms, the purpose and the executive session.
That's the completion of the Regards, the head of the meeting of the Mom City Council.
I'm just kidding.
At the end of the Regards, the head of the meeting of my life, industrial public facilities
of the audience.